mofuselocal.com 2015-05-08

# Privacy Policy » MoFuse Local » The Leader in Mobile Web Content Management

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of MoFuse, Inc. and the MoFuse Local brand (“MoFuse”, “we”, “MoFuse Local”, “our” or “us”) on the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information on [http://www.mofuse.com](http://www.mofuse.com/) or [http://www.mofuselocal.com](http://www.mofuselocal.com/) (the “Sites”) through the services, features, content or applications we offer, such as our mobile website content management platform and fast on-boarders (collectively with the Sites, the “Services”). We receive personal information about you from various sources, including: (i) if you register for the Sites and the Services, through your user account on the Services (your “Account”); (ii) your use of the Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**What does this privacy policy cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) gathered when you are using or accessing the Services.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through the Service or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

**What Personal Information do we collect?**

We collect Personal Information from you when you register on any of our sites including www.mofuse.com, *.mofuselocal.com and other related sites.

The Personal Information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of Personal Information from our users.

_Account Information:_

When you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username, password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account on the Services and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore you may not be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, but only rarely when we feel such information is important.

_User Content:_

Some features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as text, images and video for your mobile website. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account.

When ordering or registering for our services, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our sites anonymously.

**What do we use your Personal Information for?**

Any of the Personal Information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To process transactions.

To communicate with you from time to time. We enroll you to receive our quarterly email newsletter. You may opt out of receiving this newsletter at any time. From time to time there may be an email sent to your account email address because there is an important business need to do so.

We may also use Personal Information and other information collected through the Service to the extent required by law or legal process, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements (including this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service) with you, or if in our reasonable discretion use is necessary to protect our legal rights or to protect third parties. 

**How do we protect your Personal Information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your Personal Information when you place an order.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit card information is input directly to our PCI Compliant partner, Chargify hosted pages. This data is fully encrypted and shared with our Payment gateway provider database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. At no time does MoFuse, Inc. store credit card data in any of its computers, offices or hosting providers. All credit card data is stored by our PCI compliant partner, Chargify and other merchant services entities.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow this via your browser). Cookies enable the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and recall certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any Personal Information to outside parties?**

We will share your Personal Information from time to time with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also share your Personal Information with third parties with whom we have marketing arrangements with respect to the Services, and such third parties may use the Personal Information to market their products and services to you. We may release your Personal Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. In addition, we will disclose your Personal Information to any successor to our business as a result of any merger, acquisition, asset sale or similar transaction. Non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**What Information of Mine Can I Access?**

If you are a registered user, you can access Personal Information associated with your Account by logging into the Services. Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.

California Privacy Rights: Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 

MoFuse, Inc.  
2348 Post Rd Suite 202  
Warwick, RI 02886  
**Attention Privacy Department**

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are under the age of 13 years, you are not permitted to use the Services.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our websites and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Your use of the Service is subject to our Terms and Conditions , which are available at [http://mofuse.com/terms-of-service](http://mofuse.com/terms-of-service/) . This Privacy Policy forms part of our Terms and Conditions.

**Your Consent**

By using our sites, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on June 30 2013.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.mofuse.com  
MoFuse, Inc.  
2348 Post Rd Suite 202  
Warwick, RI 02886  
USA
